(Penny:)What's Mrs. Riley's chicken?
(Sheldon:)A chicken that was owned
by Mrs. Riley.
(Penny:)-Okay, forget the chicken.
-I wish I could.
(Howard:)No, no.
You may be right about me and Leonard.
Well, of course I'm right. What are the
odds I'd be wrong twice in one week?
(Penny:)No, I mean,
we can always go back to being friends.
(Sheldon:)I just said that-- This conversation
has started to circle. Meeting adjourned.
(Sheldon:)-Hello.
-Hey.
(Leonard:)What's going on?
(Sheldon:)Oh, you'd like to catch up
on the events of the day. All right.
(Sheldon:)Well, there was a half-hour wait at the
bank to get into my safe-deposit box.
(Sheldon:)I was forced to talk to Penny
about your sexual problems.
(Sheldon:)And, oh, yes, in a moment filled
with biblical resonance...
(Sheldon:)...pride wenteth before my fall...
(Sheldon:)...causing my Flash 123
to goeth to Wolowitz.
(Leonard:)Wait a minute.
You talked to Penny about our sex life?
(Sheldon:)Leonard, it astonishes me
how you continually fixate on the trivial.